3milliondogs.com 2015-02-02

# Three Million Dogs

* **Introduction**

The Three Million Dogs website ("the Website") is social networking medium that enable users to share information and content. The content is dependent upon the materials and information provided by its users.

In the course of using the Website, we may collect Personal Information and we have prepared this policy to inform you about our ongoing commitment to ensure that the Personal Information obtained during the course of our activities remains accurate and confidential.

We may from time to time review and revise our privacy practices and this Privacy Policy. Policy changes will apply to the information collected from the date of the revised Privacy Policy as well as to existing information held by us at the time of the amendment. 

* **What is Personal Information?**

We consider "Personal Information" to mean any information, recorded in any form, which allows that person, person's pets, friends or relatives to be identified. This can include your name, e-mail, gender, date of birth, photos, videos, geographic location and your interests, for example. The manner in which you use the Website is also Personal Information. For example, the network you create on the Website, the messages you post, the content you provide, the actions you take with respect to third parties' content and information uploaded, downloaded, shared, viewed, or used on the Website, the friends you make through the Website and the information that your friends may provide about you is also Personal Information. We may augment our records of your Personal Information with information collected from third party websites or directly from third parties.

Ultimately, the Personal Information you provide to the Website is at your discretion and under your control. Any Personal Information that you provide, we collect. 

* **Why Do We Collect Personal Information?**

We may use the Personal Information for the following:

  1. to determine the kind of content you would be interested in;
  2. to assist advertisers in targeting their advertising;
  3. to notify you of new product releases, service notifications or to solicit your feedback and input;
  4. to operate, maintain and manage the Website; and
  5. to fulfil our contractual or legal obligations to third parties with respect to your Personal Information.
  6. to create, promote and/or manage new websites and Applications both related and unrelated to the the Three Million Dogs brand.

* **Consent**

**By providing Personal Information on the Website, you agree and consent that we may collect, use and disclose your Personal Information in accordance with this Policy.** In addition, where appropriate, specific authorizations or consents may be obtained from time to time.

**In most cases and subject to legal and contractual restrictions, you are free to refuse or withdraw your consent at any time. It should be noted that the Website can only be used if you provide Personal Information. Consequently, if you choose not to provide us with any required Personal Information, we can not continue to allow you to use and/or have access to the Website.**

* **Children**

We use every effort to not collect Personal Information for children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not access the Website and/or provide any Personal Information to the Website. In the event that we become aware that a profile and/or any Personal Information has been created by a child under the age of 13, we shall immediately delete all Personal Information as quickly as possible and terminate the user's account.

We strongly urge that children over the age of 13 use the Website in conjunction with parental permission and parental supervision, especially with respect to divulging any Personal Information. 

* **When We May Disclose Your Personal Information**

We may disclose your Personal Information to any individual or organization in the following circumstances:

  1. to third parties who are our advisors or service providers;
  2. to third parties who are, or may be involved in maintaining, reviewing and developing our business systems, procedures and infrastructure including testing or upgrading our systems;
  3. to third parties with respect to streamlining advertisements to you that we believe would be of interest to you;
  4. to third parties in offering joint services to you; and
  5. to third parties in assisting us monitor the integrity of the Website.

Where we disclose Personal Information to third parties that perform services on our behalf, we will require those third parties to use such information solely for the purposes of providing services to us and to have appropriate safeguards for the protection of that Personal Information. 

* **The Accuracy and Retention of Personal Information**

We endeavour to ensure that any Personal Information provided and in our possession is as accurate, current and complete as necessary for the purposes for which we use that information.

We keep your Personal Information only as long as it is required for the reasons it was collected. The length of time we retain information varies, depending on its use and the nature of the information. This period may extend beyond the end of your relationship with us but it will be only for so long as it is necessary. 

* **Protection of Personal Information**

We endeavour to maintain appropriate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to the storage of Personal Information so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, or modification of Personal Information. Given the public nature of the Personal Information facilitated by the Website, we cannot control any Personal Information that may be collected by third parties.

In the event of a transfer of ownership or an acquisition of all or substantially all of our assets, we reserve the right to transfer your Personal Information. 

* **Web Site**

In using the Website, you may encounter "cookies". "Cookies" are files or pieces of information that may be stored in a computer's hard drive when an individual visits a website. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you do not wish to accept cookies, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. "Session" cookies are temporary bits of information that are erased once a visitor exits its web browser window or otherwise turn its computer off. Session cookies are used to improve navigation on websites and to collect aggregate statistical information. the Website may use session cookies.

"Persistent" cookies are more permanent bits of information that are placed on the hard drive of a visitor's computer and stays there unless it is deleted. Persistent cookies store information on a visitor's computer for a number of purposes, such as retrieving certain information previously provided (e.g., passwords), helping to determine what areas of the website visitors find most valuable, and customizing the website based on visitor preferences. Our website may use persistent cookies.

We have no control over the content of third party web sites that individuals may access through hyperlinks on the Website. We encourage everyone to read the privacy policy of every web site they visit. 

* **Resolving Your Privacy Concerns**

In the event of questions about: (i) access to your Personal Information; (ii) our collection, use, management or disclosure of Personal Information; or (iii) this Policy; please contact us by sending an e-mail to support@3milliondogs.com.

Three Million Dogs will not knowingly host content copyrighted by a third party. Violations can be reported here.
